[faint beep]
[electronic buzzing, static]
[machinery powering up]
[♪ Ominous music playing]
[electronics whirring]
[muffled rumbling]
[muffled clanging]
[boosters roaring]
[loud clanging]
[chains clanking]
[heavy thud]
[high-pitched
metallic ringing]
[crackling]
[metal groaning]
[lever buzzing]
[♪ Ominous music soars]
[♪ Music subsides]
[♪ Uneasy music playing]
[♪ Ominous
choral music playing]
[♪ Music fades]
[faint ringing]
[alarm blaring]
[sighs softly]
[announcer over PA]
Attention all workers.
Day shift starting
in T-minus 15 minutes.
Farmers to report
to mess hall immediately.
If you are experiencing
any symptoms,
such as fever, cough,
vomiting,
or difficulty breathing,
proceed to the medical bay
for examination.
- [thunder rumbles]
- [rain pattering]
The safety and well-being
of our colony
is Weyland-Yutani's
top priority.
Attention all workers...
[man] Did you hear about
the claustrophobic astronaut?
He needed space.
[woman] I'm begging you,
you got to stop.
I just spent my full share
on a belt that won't fit.
Huge waist.
See that cornbread.
[sputters] Maybe it's 'cause
I'm on this seafood diet.
I see food, I eat it.
That's so bad.
You always laughed
at that one.
Yeah, when I was 12.
[device ringing]
I'm sure it's Mr. Finch.
We owe him three months today.
He'll call again.
Well, maybe we won't be here
when he does.
[indistinct chatter]
[woman] Andy.
Stay close to me.
[revolutionist over speakers]
Wake up. Wake up now.
We're all
Weyland-Yutani slaves.
The company pays us
with food and shelter
and takes our lives
in exchange.
Don't believe their lies.
They own you!
[woman] Andy, Andy.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, Andy. Come on. Come on.
- What did I do?
- It's a scam.
The ball is never under
the cup that you pick.
It's a trick.
But how am I
gonna get the money?
Money for what?
To pay for the horse
when we get to Yvaga.
You're gonna get a horse?
I wanna call it Raindy.
Do you get it?
- Raindy.
- No, I like it.
Yeah, it's good.
Okay, so you just
wait over there.
Okay, I might be a minute.
Stay out of trouble,
all right?
[announcer over PA]
All employees will be seen.
[Andy] Good luck.
[announcer over PA]
Line up in an orderly fashion.
[officer over PA] Next.
Full name
and occupation, please.
Marie Raines Carradine, ma'am.
Farming.
It's about my travel papers.
I met my quota, and I should
be free to go now.
Right?
[officer] Go where?
Yvaga.
It's an independent system,
but it's fully terraformed.
You can actually see
the sun out there.
Where are your parents?
Uh, they died
three cycles ago.
Lung disease, from the mines.
It's just me
and my brother now.
[revolutionist over speakers]
They sell us hope
to keep us slaves.
They sell us hope to keep
us slaves. Wake up now.
[indistinct chatter]
[laughter]
[officer] I'm sorry,
but you're not eligible
for contract release yet.
Due to a shortage of workers,
you're being
transferred to the mines.
Wait, what?
No, no, no,
I reached the required hours.
You have to let me go.
Unfortunately, quotas have
been raised to 24,000 hours,
so you'll be released
from contract
in another five to six years.
Thank you, and remember
the company is really grateful
for your ongoing service.
- [Andy] Rain!
- [Rain] Hey!
Hey, stop!
Get off him! You bastards!
- [whimpering]
- I got you, I got you.
Oh, shit, you're bleeding.
Okay.
- [device beeps, cranking]
- [Rain] You're okay.
I'm resetting you.
I got you.
[gasps]
It's okay.
I shouldn't
have left you alone.
[revolutionist over speakers]
They sell us hope
to keep us slaves.
Wake up now. They own you.
[comms ringing]
[Tyler over comms] Hi, Rain.
Look, I'm sorry. I know
I've been calling you all day,
but, look,
something's come up,
and I think you should
know about it.
So, come by the trailers
and bring Andy.
[machinery thudding
and clanking]
[indistinct conversation]
Hey.
[man] Oh, for...
[automated voice over gaming
console] Game over, man.
Sup, Rain? Long time no see.
I told you she'd show up.
You owe me five bucks.
[man 2] Andy!
[door opens, whirring]
Why'd the blind miner
fall down the well?
Why?
'Cause he couldn't see
that well.
Please don't encourage him.
All right, go inside.
I'll be there in a second.
- Kay.
- Rain.
- Hi.
- Hi!
Hi.
[Kay] I missed you.
And I know my brother
missed you, too.
I'm really glad you came.
[Rain] I heard about your dad.
I'm really sorry.
Well, between the hailstorms
and the new diseases
every cycle...
Yeah, everybody's dying,
right?
So, should we show her?
Show me what?
- [system beeps]
- Okay, so, last night,
we're loading up
the last Tesotek,
we're about 200 miles
above the ground,
and then all of a sudden...
[imitates rapid beeping]
The hauler picks up
this beacon.
So Navarro tracks it,
and it turns out
there's this big Wey-Yu ship
drifting
right above our heads.
Drifting?
Decommissioned. Abandoned.
Some old relic. It's probably
damaged or obsolete.
Like that guy over there.
[Navarro] Bjorn.
Okay, just tell her.
Why are we all
sitting around here
waiting for travel permits
that the company
are never gonna give to us?
'Cause that hauler
has enough power in it
to get us to Yvaga.
Because it takes nine years
to get to Yvaga
and you can't make that trip
without cryo-sleep.
Decommissioned ships
still carry
tons of functional equipment.
And the hyperlink shows
that ship
still has a few pods left.
[chuckles in disbelief]
You want to break into
a Weyland-Yutani ship
and steal highly
regulated equipment?
Before someone else does.
[laughs]
You guys are insane.
- Well, of course we are.
- [man] No. No, we're not.
- This is...
- [Navarro] That's what I said.
[Kay] Are you gonna help us?
[hesitates] Sorry,
what do you need me for?
Andy.
- We need to use Andy.
- Andy?
[Bjorn] Mm-hmm.
[man] He's a Weyland-Yutani
synthetic. He speaks Mother.
He can access
a terminal on the ship
to get us in and out
without a fuss.
It's the only way to get in.
Okay,
but what if we get caught?
It'll ruin our chances of ever
getting a travel permit.
Right, Rain's not comin'.
Uh, how about you let us
take Andy then?
I'm not sending
my brother up there alone.
He's not your
brother though, is he?
- Bjorn, shut the fuck up.
- It's true, though, isn't it?
He's not your brother.
It's just Wey-Yu damaged goods
that your dad
found in the trash.
And that's all he is, Rain.
So just wake up.
Let's go.
- [Andy] Rain?
- [Bjorn] What?
- I didn't say anything.
- [man] Rain, wait.
I'm sorry.
Listen, I know my cousin
can be a dick sometimes,
all right?
But he is right
about something.
You need to wake up.
Because this company,
they're not gonna
give us anything.
You know that as well as I do.
We have to take it.
[♪ Somber music playing]
Rain, I just...
I don't want to end up
like our parents.
Do you?
[bird chirping]
Is it as easy as you're making
it sound, this plan of yours?
You won't even have to get out
of the Corbelan.
That much
I can promise you, okay?
Come on. What do you say?
[engines powering up]
[thunder rumbles]
[man] Bjorn, hurry up,
let's go.
All right, I'm starting
her up. Batteries on.
- [Bjorn] Lovely.
- [system powering up]
[Navarro] Could I get hydro,
please?
Comm panel.
Ground spoilers.
[man] They are armed.
[Bjorn] First time
in space, huh?
[Rain] Yeah.
[Bjorn] You too? Boop!
- [Navarro] Fuel pump.
- [man] On.
[Bjorn] Two space virgins
coming through.
[man] Right, take a good look
outside the window
'cause the way I see it,
we're never coming back.
[engines roaring]
[praying in Mandarin]
[in English] You good?
I'm good.
Yeah. It's gonna be all right.
[engines powering up]
Are you sure
this is a good idea now?
[Bjorn] Sure, Dad.
Here comes the crush.
[Corbelan rumbling]
[all laughing]
[coughing]
[Bjorn] That's how it's done,
bitch.
[Corbelan rumbling
and creaking]
[Rain exhales deeply]
[rumbling subsides]
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[gasps softly]
Is that...
Yeah.
That is our sun.
[♪ Captivating music playing]
[Kay] They say Yvaga has
the most incredible sunsets.
I've seen them.
In my dreams.
[chuckles softly]
[Andy] I can't wait
to see them with you.
[Rain] Yeah.
[Bjorn] You know, I heard that
cryo-sleep just makes years
feel like one night
of heavy drinkin' apparently.
So when we wake up
in Yvaga tomorrow,
we'll wake up with a hangover.
[sighs deeply]
There she is.
That's not a ship.
No.
[Bjorn over comms] Fuck,
that's big. What is that?
[man] Decommissioned outpost?
I don't know.
Probably got dragged
into our orbit.
Okay, Navarro,
let's get closer, please.
[Navarro] Okay.
I'm gonna match its roll.
[♪ Suspenseful music playing]
[automated voice]
Hazard proximity alert.
[Rain] What's wrong?
It's just the belt's a bit
closer than I thought.
[Navarro] How long?
It's 36 hours, give or take.
Till what?
Before the station crashes
against the rings.
[Bjorn] Sorry, what?
What did you just say?
That doesn't sound very good.
[man] 36 hours.
We should be in and out
in 30 minutes.
Yeah?
[Rain] Andy.
[Bjorn] Yeah, tops.
Are you sure
you wanna do this?
I have just one directive.
To do what's best for Rain.
Your dad wrote it.
Yeah.
That and too many dad jokes.
I'm happy...
to help.
[sighs]
Be careful out there.
[metal straining]
[man] Okay, hurry up.
We're docking in two minutes.
Put that on.
[Bjorn] Now,
why I gotta put this on for?
[man] So you don't
freeze your balls off.
[Bjorn] Mate,
you gotta stop obsessing
about my balls, man.
It's unhealthy.
[man] Keep talking
and I'll chop 'em off.
[Bjorn]Aw, you really want
'em for yourself, don't you?
Hey, you want me to show you
my balls or something?
[man] Oh, shut up a minute.
Gloves, here, take these.
[Bjorn] Hey! No.
Stop touching shit.
- Come over here.
- [man] Bjorn, leave him alone,
for fuck's sake.
Andy, take no notice.
[Bjorn] All right, okay,
won't be my fault
when he breaks somethin'.
[button beeps]
[Navarro]
There's a synth hatch
right ahead. I'm gonna dock.
[man over comms] Copy that.
Just bring us in slow.
[loud thud]
- [metal groaning]
- [device beeping]
[scanner whirring]
[man] Oh, fuck me,
it's cold in there.
What's that?
[man over comms]
It's a temp-scanner.
It's gonna lead us
to the pods.
[lever cranking]
[man] Okay, compression
is good enough.
Oxygen is too thin to breathe.
Andy...
[over comms] ...you're up.
It's your time to shine.
[chimes]
[door opens]
[chuckles] Yes! Andy!
Beautiful work.
Okay.
[laughs]
[Bjorn] Congrats.
You're not a virgin anymore.
[man] All right.
[air blowing]
[man] Okay, let's go.
[Bjorn grunting]
[Bjorn] Fuck.
[Tyler] Guys, it looks like
we're in zero-g.
[Bjorn] Yeah, I can feel it
in my stomach.
- [machinery whirring]
- [gravity generators warbling]
Wait, what's that?
Gravity generators.
When offline, they still purge
themselves every few minutes.
[Tyler] Prevents the place
from blowing up.
[gravity generators warbling]
[Bjorn]Oh, fuck me,
there goes my stomach again.
[Tyler] Okay, straight ahead.
[♪ Suspenseful music playing]
[Tyler] According
to the scanner,
the pods should be in here.
[panting] Jesus.
Andy, you good?
[Andy] Yeah.
[Tyler] All right, great news.
I've got eyes on the pods.
[gravity generators pulsing]
Fuck!
[Bjorn grunts]
[Tyler] Bjorn, you okay?
[Bjorn] Fuck! [groans]
I think I fractured
my asshole.
[gravity generators warbling]
Fuckin' hell. Don't fuck
with this gravity purge, man.
[chimes]
[system beeping]
[Tyler] Thank God,
there's still
some power left in this relic.
[machinery powering up]
[Tyler] Okay, watch out.
Gravity's coming back.
[Bjorn grunts] Fuckin' hell.
[pods hissing]
[Tyler] All right, here we go.
Let's see what we got.
Okay.
- Shit.
- What's the problem?
Pods don't have enough fuel.
What do you mean?
[Tyler] They're loaded up
for three years in stasis.
[Bjorn] Yeah,
but it takes nine years
to get to Yvaga, mate.
[Tyler]Yeah, I know, I know.
I'm aware of that.
[Bjorn] Fuckin' hell.
I knew it. I fuckin' knew it.
- I knew it.
- [Tyler] Just relax.
Maybe you guys
should just come back.
[Tyler] No, no,
we're not givin' up now.
[Bjorn] Yvaga's
the nearest system.
So what are we supposed
to do now? Huh?
- What are we gonna do?
- [Tyler] Shut up.
Okay, strong reading.
Must be a cryo depot nearby.
We should find
more fuel there.
Navarro, I'm ejecting the EEV.
Come on, Andy.
You guys pick it up
while we get the cryo-fuel.
[Tyler] Hold.
Yeah, 400 yards away,
dead ahead.
What's with the military shit?
What?
[Bjorn]
All that military shit.
- Well, it's effective.
- Is it? [snickers]
- And cool.
- It's not very cool.
You just look like a twat.
- [Andy] I'm sorry.
- [Tyler] All right, chill.
Let's keep it movin'.
[Bjorn] if you do that again,
I'll fuck you up.
- [Rain] Bjorn, back off!
- [Bjorn] You understand?
Just as long as he stays
out of my way.
Why is he being
such a dick to him?
Because of what happened
to his mom.
- What do you mean?
- [Navarro] Last cycle,
there was a gas leak
in the mines,
so a synthetic made the call
to seal them
with Bjorn's mom
still trapped inside.
What?
Synthetics can't harm humans.
It sacrificed three miners
to save a dozen.
That, they can do.
That's terrible.
[engine revving]
[♪ Intriguing music playing]
Subtitle | www.movieddl.me
I got you, I got you.
Come on, come on, come on.
Easy, easy.
Good job.
[Kay retches]
- [vomiting]
- [Rain] Kay!
Kay! Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm right here.
I'm right here. You're okay.
[Kay breathing heavily]
[Navarro] I'm gonna go
check on the pods.
[hatch door whirring]
[Kay] No, no. Don't worry.
I'm not sick.
[Rain] What's wrong, then?
[Kay] Nothing is.
Oh, girl.
Who's the father?
Some asshole.
Just don't tell my brother,
okay?
He has enough things
to worry about.
No. I won't say anything.
I'm just happy this baby
will get to see the sun.
[♪ Stirring music playing]
[scanner whirring]
[Tyler] I think
we're almost there.
Okay, Navarro.
Airlock 5-B,
that's our way out
once we find this cryo-fuel.
[Navarro] On my way.
[automated voice over PA]
Welcome to the
Renaissance Space Station,
the center of Weyland-Yutani
Research and Development.
The station
is divided into two halves,
Romulus and Remus,
each dedicated
to our quest to improve
mankind's role in outer space.
This place
gives me the creeps.
Did you hear about the miner
who lost his left side?
He's all right now.
Do you get it? He's all right.
[Bjorn] Can you turn
yourself off, please?
You said you were nervous
and I was trying
to make sure you were...
Jesus! You know, I can't
wait to get in them pods
and never see you again,
you know that?
[Andy] You'll see me in Yvaga.
[Bjorn]No,
you're not going to Yvaga.
[Tyler] Bjorn, stop!
I'm not?
Well done.
Oh, she didn't tell you?
Yeah, yeah, it's a
non-Weyland-Yutani system,
so no fake people allowed.
I prefer the term
"artificial person" myself.
Andy, look.
[over comms]
Rain could end up in prison
if she takes you with her.
And if you guys
stay in Jackson,
it's just a matter of time
before you get decommissioned
again by the company.
You understand?
I need you on the ship
to guard the pods.
But once we get there...
[Bjorn] Decommish.
Lights out for good.
[object clatters]
You done?
[Bjorn]
Just tellin' the truth.
That's okay.
If it's what's best for Rain,
it's what's best for me.
You're a good guy, Andy.
We're all gonna miss you.
[Navarro] So he didn't know?
I just did not
have the heart to tell him.
[Navarro]
You shouldn't feel bad.
[softly] Shit.
[Navarro]
You're not gonna throw
your whole life away
for Andy's sake.
[sighs]
He doesn't care.
It doesn't matter to him.
Okay? He's not...
you know, real.
[♪ Solemn music playing]
[♪ Ominous music builds]
[Tyler] The signal's
coming from in here.
[Rain] Thought you said
this place was decommissioned.
[Tyler] Yeah.
[Rain] Doesn't look
decommissioned to me.
[Tyler] No, it doesn't.
But it's definitely deserted.
- [Taser powering up]
- Hey, Andy, look at this.
I could probably fry a
synthetic with one of these...
if I just amp up the juices.
[crackling]
Hey, you know, I might
take this with me, actually.
[Tyler] All right, enough.
Just in case you have
any fucking funny ideas.
[gasping] It's a joke.
I was joking.
What the fuck?
Watch out.
[Tyler] Shit.
It's only a synthetic.
[chuckles nervously]
Fuck. [exhales]
I thought it was a real person
there for a second.
[Navarro]
What happened in there?
[Tyler] Don't know.
A chemical spill, maybe.
The fuel must be in that room.
Let's grab it
and get the fuck out of here.
[Tyler] All right. Andy?
[lock chiming]
[door creaking]
[Tyler] Bjorn,
take the torch please.
[Bjorn] I don't think
there's any pods in here.
[Tyler] Nah,
just cooling equipment.
Uses the same type of fuel,
though.
[beeping]
Yes.
- [exhales]
- [Tyler] Forty-five Ks.
It's more than enough fuel
to get us to Yvaga.
Right. Bjorn, give me
a hand with this, please.
[grunts]
[Tyler] Bjorn, pull it out
on three, all right?
- Ready?
- [Bjorn] Uh-huh.
[Tyler] One, two...
- three.
- [air hissing]
[Bjorn groans] Fuck!
- Fuck.
- My fingers.
[alarm blares]
I can't feel my fingers.
It really hurts.
Just froze my hands off
- What's happening?
- [Bjorn] Fuck.
[Tyler] Don't know. It's some
kind of emergency lockdown.
Andy, the door.
Shit, he doesn't
have the clearance.
What does that mean?
[Tyler] Doesn't have the
clearance to open the door.
So you're trying
to tell me that
he can fucking reboot
the entire ship,
but can't open
a random fucking door
to a random room?
Well, obviously,
that's no random room.
[Bjorn straining] Come on!
Come on!
[alarm continues blaring]
[Navarro] Hey, don't worry.
We'll get 'em out of there.
If Andy
can't open those doors,
I doubt
we'll have better luck.
He's a Weyland-Yutani
synthetic
and we're just trespassing.
[indistinct announcement
over PA]
Yeah, so you got any ideas?
[Rain] Not yet.
[Navarro]
I think it's in here.
Bjorn!
Tyler!
They're in there.
Hey, what are you doing?
If this module
is still working,
I can try to transfer
its credentials to Andy.
A higher clearance
should open that door.
[alarm blaring]
[♪ Foreboding music playing]
[cryo-fuel hissing]
[squelching]
Shit. It's stuck.
It's so hot in here, man.
[♪ Ominous music playing]
Whoa.
Sick.
Yeah, maybe try not to touch
anything in here.
[Navarro] Yeah, okay, Mom.
[yelps]
[synthetic screeching]
Help me! Help!
Oh, no! What do I do?
The module. Take it out!
[both panting]
You okay?
That was fucked up.
Here.
[Rain] Let me see.
Yes, okay.
[Tyler] All right.
- Got it.
- [Rain] Hey.
Rain.
This is from that synthetic.
Try putting it
on Andy's module.
I'm so sorry.
Let's just get outta here.
Andy?
All right, let's see.
Okay.
- [Andy gasps]
- Fuck.
Rain, did I do something
wrong? He's just frozen up.
[Rain] He's just rebooting.
It's gonna take
a couple of minutes.
[squeaking]
[squelching]
[Tyler] Here, let me get you
something for those fingers.
[water splashes]
The fuck was that?
All right,
stay there a second.
[Rain] Tyler?
[Navarro] Hey,
what are you guys doing?
[creature chittering]
[gasps] Bjorn?
Stop playing around, man.
Just get up.
[Bjorn] I'm not
playing around.
There's something
in the water.
[Navarro] What do you mean?
What is it?
I don't know.
I don't know what it is.
There's something
in the fuckin' water.
[screams]
[grunting]
Bjorn!
- [gasps]
- [Navarro gasps] Fuck!
[Navarro] What the fuck
was that?
[Tyler gasping]
Andy!
[grunting]
Bjorn!
[♪ Tense music playing]
Bjorn, help him! Do something!
[Tyler] Bjorn!
[Taser crackling]
- [Rain] Tyler!
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[grunts]
Come on!
- Come on! Help me!
- No, stop. Stop. Don't...
- No! Navarro!
- Those things will get out.
If they come in here...
If they come in...
- If they come...
- [Rain] No!
Fuck. Fuck.
[chittering]
[exhales sharply, gasps]
[creature screeching]
[Tyler] Andy! Let's go!
Go! Bjorn!
Andy, the door!
- Bjorn!
- [Rain] Come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on!
[Navarro] Get out of there!
[Rain] Come on, come on,
come on!
- Come on, come on, come on!
- [Tyler] Go, go, go!
Get out of there!
Go! Go!
- [Navarro] Bjorn, come on!
- [Tyler] Go! Go!
[glass thudding, cracking]
[Navarro shouting]
[Rain] Andy, the door!
[Navarro screaming]
[muffled screaming]
[Tyler] Stay still.
Stay still.
[Bjorn] I know!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[muffled grunting]
[Rain] It's choking her.
Stop! You gotta stop! Hey!
- It's choking her!
- [Tyler] Shit.
Stop! Bjorn!
Bjorn, stop!
For fuck's sake, stop!
- Stop!
- What's it doin'?
Is it fuckin' killin' her?
[Andy] I do not believe that's
what the creature is doing.
No.
[Rain] Andy?
Based on the rhythmic
dilatation of those bladders,
and its synchronization
to her breathing patterns,
I'd surmise it's feeding her
oxygen to keep her alive.
For what purpose,
I do not know.
Sorry, who the fuck are you?
I'm an ND-255
Weyland-Yutani synthetic.
Originally built for mining
and safety tasks.
You guys call me Andy.
It's that module.
Yes.
That new module didn't
just upgrade my credentials.
It substantially
updated my AI,
and it's mending my motor
systems as we speak.
A most overdue upgrade,
I must say.
Shit. I'mma fucking
fry this thing.
- [Rain] Okay, wait.
- Don't!
- Why not?
- That amount of current
will violently
contract its tail flexors
and will break her neck.
So what,
you got a better idea?
What should we
fucking do then, huh?
Hey, hey. Hey! Hey, hey.
Andy, do you know
how to help her?
I'm afraid my
knowledge database
has not really changed.
I do not know
what this creature is
or how to remove it safely.
But there's someone
in this room who might.
[machine powering up]
[cable clicks]
[synthetic powering up]
[synthetic glitching]
I need to secure
Z-01 compound.
Mission's priority. All other
priorities rescinded.
Must complete the mission.
I'm sorry...
but your mission has failed.
[synthetic] What? No, I...
Can you tell us
what we can do to help her?
You don't help her. You run.
Get out, however you got in.
[Bjorn] No, no, no.
Wait, whoa, whoa.
Nah, we're not fuckin' leavin'
her, okay? You understand?
Then have mercy
and end her life now.
If not, you all die.
[Bjorn] So what the fuck
is he ea yin'?
What's it doing to her?
The parasitoid is implanting
the Plagiarus Praepotens
in her.
I beg your pardon?
A seed that will amalgamate
with her DNA
and rapidly grow out of her.
What's gonna grow out of her?
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
XX121 Xenomorph.
One of our towing ships
first made contact with this
specimen two decades ago.
Of the seven crew members
aboard the USS Nostromo,
only one survived,
blowing the creature
out of the airlock.
We've been searching
for it ever since.
170 days ago,
our search came to an end
and the body of the Xenomorph
was brought on board...
presumed dead.
But of course,
lack of oxygen and food is
of no true consequence to this
perfect organism.
Yet nothing is truly immortal.
Clearly.
It wreaked havoc
over this station,
until what was left of our
security forces shot it dead.
Only to trigger its swan song.
Acid for blood?
Sulfuric and hydrofluoric.
I sealed the station back up,
but it was too late.
[Bjorn] Hey, shut up!
Nobody cares about your
fucking ship anymore.
Okay, okay. Okay.
What if we use the cryo-fuel
to freeze
the root of the tail?
Maybe if it's frozen,
it won't choke her.
That could work.
[♪ Tense music playing]
[cryo-fuel hisses]
[parasitoid squelching]
[sighs shakily]
[parasitoid screeching]
[squelching]
[Tyler] All right, get it off!
Get it off!
- [parasitoid squealing]
- [Tyler grunts]
[Tyler panting]
[Navarro screaming]
[Rain] It's gone. It's off
of you. It's off of you.
[Rain shushing]
It's off. It's off. It's off.
- [Rain shushing]
- You're okay. You're okay.
[synthetic]
I wouldn't be so sure.
What are the odds?
60 to 40 against your friend.
What are the odds on what?
That the creature's
finished its job already.
[weakly] What is he
talking about?
[synthetic] Listen to me.
Humans go through
too many emotional stages
before accepting the cold,
yet rational - sometimes
hardest - path.
You must help them.
[indistinct chatter]
[Rain] Andy?
- What's going on?
- I'm sorry
but we can't let her back
on the ship.
- Oh, yeah? That is a problem.
- What're you doing?
- You must understand.
- [Bjorn] You see?
That's what I mean
by "funny ideas"!
[Rain] What're you talking
about? No, he's...
- [Rain] No! No!
- You fuckin' bitch!
Hey! Andy! Andy!
[Bjorn] We're gonna go.
[Rain] Hey, hey, hey!
I'm right here.
Let's go, let's go. Come on.
Tyler, let's go, man! Come on!
- [Rain] I'm here.
- [Tyler] Bjorn! No.
Bjorn, we're not leaving
without them!
- [Rain] I'm here.
- [Tyler] Bjorn!
[♪ Tense music playing]
- Where are they?
- You need to listen.
We have to start the ship,
okay?
- Just go and start the ship.
- Where's Rain? How...
Forgive me.
I've been nothing
but a burden to you.
Today, I can finally help.
And you won't see me
as a child anymore.
[Rain] What?
Andy!
[♪ Suspenseful music playing]
- [metal straining]
- [Bjorn grunts]
- [Rain] Hey!
- [Tyler] Bjorn!
[panting]
[Bjorn grunting]
[Navarro] Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Navarro, undock!
Undock the ship!
[automated voice]
Undocking initiated.
Please clear the airlock.
[alarm blaring]
What the fuck is he doing?
They can't
just leave without us.
He thinks Andy's
trying to kill Navarro.
What?
Wait, is he?
I don't know.
[Rain] Andy? Andy?
[Rain knocking on door]
Andy, open the door.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't stop them.
Bjorn?
[over comms]
Bjorn, what are you doing?
You can't just leave us here.
You gotta come back
and get us.
Sorry, I can't do that until
she turns that psychopath off.
[Kay] What's going on?
[Navarro] Andy, uh...
- Andy, he's glitchy.
- [Kay] What?
[Navarro] I just need
to get away
from this airlock right now.
I just need...
[Kay] Navarro?
Are you all right?
What's wrong?
What do you need?
[breathes shakily]
[Kay] Navarro?
[groaning]
- [bones cracking]
- [Navarro grunts]
[Kay gasps]
[weakly] Oh, God.
[Kay] Oh, my God,
what is that?
Navarro, please.
Navarro! Navarro!
Hey, hey, hey.
[Navarro choking]
I don't know what to do,
I'm sorry. I don't know.
[engines powering up]
- Someone talk to me!
- [Kay sobbing over comms]
[Tyler] Kay, Bjorn, Navarro,
what's going on?
[grunting]
[Kay] Help!
- Help!
- [Navarro] Kay!
[Kay] What's happening?
What's happening?
[weakly]
Please don't let me die.
[Kay] Someone help!
[Navarro grunting]
[screaming]
[gasps]
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
- [explosion]
- [station rumbling]
[gasps]
[squealing]
[panting]
- [screams]
- [metal screeching]
[grunts, screams]
[Tyler gasping]
[air whooshing]
Bjorn?
Kay?
We have to go get them.
[automated voice] T-minus-47
minutes to impact event.
Doesn't make any sense.
No, I thought you said
we had hours.
The explosion pushed
the station's axis off
by a few degrees,
just enough to hit the
asteroid belt a lot sooner.
[Rain] Where did they crash?
Romulus Hangar Bay,
on the other side
of the station.
- Okay.
- [Tyler] Let's go.
[automated voice] T-minus-45
minutes to impact event.
Mother. What's the integrity
of Compound Z-01 ?
There's still hope.
[Tyler] We need to find a way
to cross
to the Romulus module.
- [Rain gasps]
- [parasitoid screeching]
[Tyler] No, no, no.
[Rain] They must've spread
from the lab.
[Tyler] I don't see
another way.
Andy, can...
[Andy] I heard your voice
in my head.
Calling.
[synthetic] ND-255
artificial person.
Your model
was once the backbone
of our colonization efforts,
and it's an honor to be
in your presence.
Please allow me
to introduce myself.
I'm Science Officer Rook,
and I humbly request
your services now.
I'm afraid I have
just one directive.
To do what's best for...
Your upgrade came
with a new directive.
It overrides the old one.
I see.
What's required of me...
Sir?
To finish our mission.
[♪ Ominous music playing]
- [Rain] Andy!
- [Tyler] Andy!
Andy.
[Andy] My apologies.
I was consulting my friend
about our situation.
Follow me.
[Tyler] What? Our situation?
How do you...
Andy! Andy!
[electricity crackling]
[Andy] The parasitoids
have no eyes.
They track you by sound,
but primarily,
by heat signature.
What?
Your body temperature.
[Tyler] Right.
If we raise the temperature
in the room
to match our bodies,
would that make us
invisible to them?
If we're quiet enough?
Just one way to find out.
Hey.
This is all my fault.
[Tyler sighs deeply]
Yeah, it is.
Yours, mine,
and everyone else's.
We all decided
to do this together.
We'll get to them.
[alarm blaring]
[automated voice] T-minus
40 minutes to impact event.
[breathing weakly]
[whimpering]
[distorted beeping]
[Andy] The hallway's
temperature
is now equal to your bodies,
so the creatures should not
be able to see you.
But stress, fear, panic will
spike your temperature
and you'll be exposed.
Sweat, goosebumps.
That's your skin trying to
cool your body down.
So watch out for those.
Now, stay calm and stay quiet.
[parasitoids scuttling]
[parasitoids chittering]
- [parasitoids scuttling]
- [gasps softly]
[electricity crackling]
- [loud electric crackling]
- [gasps softly]
[Tyler shushing softly]
[breathing shakily]
- [loud bang]
- [gasps softly]
[electricity buzzing]
[squelching]
[liquid dripping]
[breathing shakily]
[muffled gasp]
[squelching]
[cable clicks]
[machinery powering up]
[crackling]
[squelching]
- [muffled crackling]
- [grunting]
- [muffled screeching]
- Come on. Come on!
Come on! Come on!
[gasping]
[Xenomorph screeching]
[Kay] Okay. Okay.
Bjorn, let's go. Let's go.
[sizzling]
[panting]
- [screams]
- [gasps]
Fuck!
Stay back, stay back, please.
- [flesh sizzling]
- [groaning]
Fuck!
- [flesh sizzling]
- [groans]
No! Fuck!
[♪ Tense music playing]
[continues groaning]
[grunts]
[♪ Foreboding music playing]
[breath trembling]
[whimpering]
[squelching]
[breathing shakily]
[Kay over comms] Tyler.
Come on.
[scuttling nearby]
[whispers] Kay...
[sobbing] Oh, my God, Tyler...
[Tyler whispers]
Kay, I'm here. I'm here.
[Kay] Please, Tyler, help me.
Everyone's dead.
I can't open this door.
Please.
[gasps]
[whispers] The lever
with the red button,
there's a key to the left.
[Kay] Help.
I can't find it.
There's not a key.
There isn't a key, Tyler.
[Tyler whispers] It'll be
there. It has to be there.
A key. Okay, okay.
[grunts]
Uh... [whimpers]
[♪ Menacing music plays]
I have the key.
Oh, my God.
[grunting]
[screaming]
[thud echoes]
Run.
[Tyler] Go! Go!
[Rain and Tyler panting]
[♪ Tense music playing]
[Rain yelps]
[Rain shouting indistinctly]
[Rain] Wait!
[Tyler] Wait!
- Come on!
- [grunts]
[both panting]
You almost closed
the door on him.
Yes, but I didn't.
I calculated
the timing perfectly
with more success
than last time.
Won't you agree?
We're getting close.
Let's move.
[automated voice] T-minus
30 minutes to impact event.
[groans]
[pipe clanks]
[groaning]
[breathing heavily]
[whimpers]
- [metal creaking]
- [grunts]
- [thudding]
- [gasps]
[breathing shakily]
[metal thudding]
[hissing and snarling]
[automated voice]
Access denied.
[alarm blaring]
[panting]
- [door thuds]
- [muffled] Kay...
We're here. We're here.
It's all right,
it's all right,
it's all right.
Andy, open the door.
It's all right.
We're gonna get you out.
[muffled] Tyler,
open the door.
Open the door. Come on.
Oh, my God.
[Tyler] Look at me. Kay,
Kay, Kay. Look at me.
- [Rain] Andy, open the door.
- Kay, look at me. Look at me.
It's all right.
I'm gonna get you out.
Andy, open the door.
Stop fucking around.
- [Rain] What are you doing?
- [Tyler] Don't look
- over there. Andy.
- [Kay]Tyler, what's wrong?
Hey, I need you to open
that door right now, okay?
That's what the creature's
waiting for us to do.
- [Kay] Open it, please.
- [snarling]
[Tyler] Andy.
Andy, open the door.
Listen to me.
Listen to me. She's pregnant.
[Kay] Just, please.
Guys, please. Come on.
[Rain] She's gonna
have a baby. Okay?
- Do you hear what I'm saying?
- [Andy] It takes that door
two seconds to open,
another two to fully close.
[Kay] What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Come on,
what are you doing? Please...
That's plenty of time for the
creature to get in here.
[Kay] Please, please,
please open the door.
- Why won't you help me?
- [muffled] Listen, listen.
- Come on, help me, please.
- You have to run right now.
- Please, please.
- Run. Run.
You're one of us, man.
You're one of us!
[Rain] Kay, it's the only way.
- Open the fucking door. Andy!
- [Rain] You have to
- fucking run. All right?
- [Tyler] Andy, please!
- [Rain] It's the only way.
- [Tyler] Andy!
- [Rain] You have to run!
- [Kay] Please!
- [Tyler] Open the fucking...
- [muffled scream]
- [Xenomorph screeching]
- [Tyler] Kay! Kay!
No, no, no.
Kay!
[Tyler sobbing]
[yells]
[Tyler mumbling] I'll open it.
She's all right. She's moving.
No. It's all right.
[Rain sobbing]
[Tyler] Andy,
open the door, please.
Andy, I need to go
and get her.
I'm truly sorry.
There was nothing I could
have done to save her.
You could have opened
the fucking door! [yells]
We'd all be dead if I had.
We need to move
before the creature
finds its way into this room.
[Rain] Andy...
what's your prime directive?
I'm afraid
I have a new directive.
To do what's best
for the company.
[breathing shakily]
I need to remove that module.
I'm afraid that's not in the
best interest of the company.
We need to move.
Now.
How could you do that?
What?
Leave someone behind?
Where are we going?
To finish a task Rook
has entrusted upon me.
When completed,
he'll clear the Corbelan
for departure and open
the docking bay doors.
You will be free to continue
to Yvaga together.
And I'll return to Jackson.
And stay in Jackson.
That is, assuming
we make it out of here alive.
We're here.
[door levers cranking]
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[automated voice]
Romulus Beta Lab.
All personnel require
A-1 security clearance.
[Rain] What is that?
Probably some fucked up
bio-weapon, I'm sure.
[Rook over monitor]
Actually, quite the opposite.
Andy, tell them.
Tell them what I told you.
[Andy] Our colonies are dying.
Unbearable temperatures,
novel diseases every cycle.
Toxic mine fumes.
It's all one unforeseen
tragedy after the other.
Mankind was never truly suited
for space colonization.
They're simply too fragile.
They're too weak.
The work of this station
aimed to change that.
"The perfect organism."
That's how we should
refer to human beings.
So, I set this wrong right.
I took its gift for humanity.
Inside the parasitoids
I bio engineered
from the Xenomorph's DNA,
I discovered a unique
non-Newtonian fluid.
Life.
In its most primal,
unadulterated form.
This microorganism
can be the most
destructive pathogen
ever observed.
But acetylated
and synthesized in our lab,
I've turned it
into the miracle
Mr. Weyland died
searching for.
Prometheus fire.
The divine gift to humanity.
Z-01 contains
the genome responsible
for the Xeno's ability
to accelerate
and slow down
its metabolism at will.
Its symbiotic capableness
easily rewrites
the host's DNA
through its blood.
This is a much needed and well
overdue upgrade for humanity.
We simply cannot wait
for evolution anymore.
Yeah, can we
get out of here now?
My mission is to take
this back to the colony
for further development.
Rook is tracking the compound.
When detected inside our ship,
he'll open
the docking bay doors
and set the hauler on
autopilot back to the colony.
Wait.
Do you see it?
There.
The fucking thing's
huntin' us.
[Andy] Right. New plan.
Can you manage yourself
with a gun?
Yes, I fucking can.
Right, this is an
F44AA pulse rifle.
It's rotating breech,
electronic pulse action.
It's what the
Colonial Marines used.
AA stands for Aiming Assist.
So, right,
you put that under your arm.
[rifle clicks]
That's it.
Right, this hand here.
All right.
Aim it towards Andy.
Pull the trigger haltway.
Don't worry, the safety's on.
[rifle chiming, clicks]
See?
Aiming assistance.
If that thing
comes towards you,
you point it in its general
direction, you'll never miss.
- Where'd you learn all this?
- Uh...
Games and magazines.
You've just got one mag.
That's it.
450 rounds.
[Andy] And you mustn't fire
a single one.
Acid for blood. Remember?
We're on the bottom floor
of the station.
Below our feet
is the vacuum of space.
You shoot that creature
and it's a guaranteed
instant decompression.
And we all die.
So what's the point
in giving us the guns?
Because the creature
may see it as a threat,
and maybe won't charge at us
dead on.
Maybe.
Big maybe.
I found us a way
through the conveyor belt.
This way.
Andy.
Are you there?
[rat squeaking]
[automated voice] T-minus
20 minutes to impact event.
[Andy] There's a lift
at the end of this corridor.
It will take us
directly to our ship.
[Rain] There's more
of those things.
Yeah, that's not good.
[Andy] They seem to have been
here for quite some time.
[Rain] Andy?
[lever clicks]
[Rain breathing shakily]
[lights switching on]
[gasps]
[softly] Jesus Christ.
[♪ Sinister music playing]
[Andy] Busy little creatures.
I think we better go back
and find another way.
That might be a good idea.
[Rain] Andy,
see if you can open this gate.
- [heavy breathing in distance]
- [Tyler] Stop.
[Rain] What?
[groaning echoing]
Kay!
[Rain] Hey!
Tyler!
[Tyler] Kay!
Kay!
[gasping]
[♪ Eerie music playing]
[Tyler] Kay!
I got her, I got her.
It's all right. We got you.
She's alive.
[Tyler and Rain grunting]
[Tyler] Okay, we got you,
we got you.
[Rain] Hold on.
[Tyler grunts] Okay.
[Kay groaning weakly]
[Tyler] We're here,
we're here.
Tyler, she's losing
a lot of blood.
[Andy] Maybe that's why
she hasn't been implanted yet.
[Tyler]How do you know?
There's no dead
parasitoid by her feet.
Andy, this is on you.
So you do something.
Please! Andy!
[Andy] 25% of the human genome
is shared with rats.
And it worked on the rat.
[breathing weakly]
[Tyler] Come on, Kay.
[Rain] Don't.
What choice do I have?
We take her back to the hauler
and we put her
in the cryo-pod. Okay?
That will keep her alive
long enough to
get her proper treatment
back at the colony.
I don't trust this.
Andy, will she make it?
If we hurry.
[screeching]
[distant screeching]
[rifle powering up]
[♪ Tense music playing]
[Rain] Go! Go!
[Rain] I see it. I see it.
[Tyler] This is it,
this is it.
[Rain] I got her.
I got her. I got her.
[Rain] You're okay.
You're okay.
We're so close.
[Kay wincing and groaning]
Hey. Hey, you're okay.
Hey, we're almost there.
We're almost there.
You see, you're so close.
You just gotta hang in there.
[Tyler] Watch out!
- [Xenomorph screeching]
- [gasps]
[Tyler groans]
[Rain] Tyler?
- [Kay whimpering]
- Tyler!
- [Andy grunts]
- [Rain wails]
[Tyler screaming]
[Xenomorph hissing]
[Xenomorphs snarling]
[yelling]
Is that all you got?
[snarling]
[Tyler yelling]
[both gasping]
- [Rain] Andy!
- [Xenomorph snarling]
[gasping]
[shuddering]
No! Tyler!
[grunting]
[elevator whirring]
[sobbing]
[♪ Somber music playing]
[Andy shuddering]
[elevator stops]
Kay, Kay, listen to me, okay?
This goes
straight to our ship.
I need you to take this.
And get into a cryo-pod.
And autopilot will fly you
back to our colony.
Can you do that?
[Kay sniffling]
Yes?
What about you?
I'll find a way back.
[sniffles]
[Kay sobbing]
[elevator starts]
[sobbing]
[winces]
[autoinjector clicks]
[lever clanks]
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[gasps]
[distant screeching]
[Andy whimpering]
[shuddering]
Let me take it out.
And I'll fix you in return.
Listen to me.
You'll die in here
and that's not
in the best interest
of the company or mine.
- [module shuts down]
- [Andy whimpering]
[device cranking, beeping]
[whimpering stops]
Come on. Andy, please.
[alarm blares]
[automated voice] T-minus
10 minutes to impact event.
Rain?
Andy.
- I'm so, so sorry.
- No, no.
No, I'm sorry.
[Xenomorph screeching nearby]
[Xenomorph screeching]
[rifle powering up]
[Rain] It won't
hold them off for long.
[screeching]
[Xenomorphs screeching]
[grunting]
Come on.
[Rook] You're
wasting your time.
Hey. Hey. Please help us.
Open the door.
I'm afraid
I must deny your petition.
I just can't risk
compromising the compound.
But know that I'm grateful
for the invaluable help
you two have provided
to the company.
[grunting]
[Rain] Son of a bitch!
- [button clicking]
- Andy, open it.
- [Andy] Here.
- [Rain] Open.
- It's not working.
- [yells]
God damn it!
- [Xenomorphs screeching]
- [Rain gasps]
I can't lie
about your chances,
but you have my sympathies.
- [Rain gasps]
- [Xenomorphs screeching]
[Kay groaning]
[wheezing]
- [button beeping]
- [Rook] Press it,
so I can take control of your
ship and fly you out of here.
[weakly] Who are you?
A friend.
Your companions died
so you could live.
Press the button...
and let me
honor their sacrifice.
Andy, can you tell me
one of your jokes?
Why don't monsters eat clowns?
[Xenomorphs approaching]
- 'Cause they taste funny.
- They taste funny.
I don't understand
cloning at all.
That makes two of us.
I read a great book
about zero gravity.
- I just couldn't put it down.
- Couldn't put it down.
Rain?
Rain, what are you doing?
I'm turning off
the gravity generator.
[automated voice]
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five,
four, three,
two, one.
[gravity generators warbling]
[snarling]
Rain, are you sure about this?
Only one way to find out.
[target locking]
It works.
[rifle firing]
[Xenomorphs screeching]
- [Andy] Rain! You're at 40%.
- [Rain yells]
[Andy] 20%.
[gunfire]
[Xenomorphs screeching]
- [parasitoid chittering]
- Rain!
Oh, fuck.
[blood sizzling]
Stay behind me.
Andy, be careful.
[blood sizzling]
Rain!
Andy, you okay?
[panting]
We need
to get to the elevator.
The elevator won't work
without gravity.
[whirring]
[Rain] Ready?
[grunting]
- [gasps]
- [Xenomorph snarling]
- [Andy] Rain!
- [grunts]
[Rain yelling]
[grunting, screams]
- [♪ Tense music playing]
- [sizzling]
[grunting] Fuck.
[Andy grunts]
No.
[alarm blaring]
[Andy] It's a gravity purge!
Andy!
Come on.
[gasping]
[Rain screaming]
- [Xenomorph snarling]
- [whimpers]
- [hissing]
- [♪ sinister music playing]
[sizzling]
[explosion]
[♪ Tense music playing]
[air whooshing]
- [grunts]
- [screeching]
[gasps]
- [grunts]
- [elevator thudding]
[snarling]
[Rain] Andy!
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[screeching]
[yelping]
[gunshot]
[yelps]
Get away from her.
[screeching]
You bitch.
[♪ Triumphant music playing]
[chuckles softly]
[automated voice]
impact event in 10,
nine, eight,
seven, six,
five,
- four, three...
- Come on.
...two, one.
[Rain] Kay.
[panting]
What took you so long?
Let's get you outta here.
I'm glad to see
you two made it.
[boosters roaring]
[metal groaning]
[Rain] I got you.
Watch your head.
- Thank you.
- You're gonna be just fine.
Both of you.
The company
couldn't be prouder
of what's been
accomplished here today.
I've sent
a message back to HQ.
When received in six months,
they'll travel
to Jackson's Star
to retrieve the compound from
you for further development.
What are you doing?
Change of plans.
Andy, stop her.
Reconnect us now.
No, no, no.
You two cannot do this.
The compound must be delivered
to the company.
I'm afraid
I must deny your petition.
- Have a nice day.
- [static]
Now you better listen to me
here, now, you two.
You are insignificant in the
great scheme of things. You...
[station rumbling]
No.
This will keep your systems
online until we get to Yvaga.
- But I thought that...
- I don't care.
You're coming with me.
All right?
If that's
what's best for Rain.
Andy, I have
a new directive for you.
Do what's best for us.
Done.
Good.
[cryo-fuel hissing]
[alarm chiming]
No.
[grunting]
[gasps] Kay. Kay.
What's wrong?
- [squelching]
- Oh, no, no.
[yells in agony]
[♪ Tense music playing]
[Kay screaming]
[screaming]
[squelching]
[gasping]
[screaming]
Get it away from me.
[wailing]
[grunts]
[sizzling]
[grunting]
- [gasps softly]
- [baby cooing]
[engine powers down]
[gasps]
[alarm blaring]
[grunts]
[softly] Oh, my God.
[♪ Eerie music playing]
[electricity crackling]
[Kay groaning weakly]
[cryo-pod whirring]
- [gasping softly]
- [♪ tense music intensifies]
[♪ Music stops]
[alarm blaring faintly]
[whimpering]
[footsteps thudding]
[metal thudding]
[bones cracking]
- [snarling]
- [gasps]
[Kay screaming]
- [♪ Tense music resumes]
- [gasps]
[Rain] Kay.
[crying]
No. Please, please.
- [sniffing]
- [Kay sobbing]
[hissing]
[Kay wailing]
[Andy whimpering]
[Rain] Andy! Andy!
No, no, no.
Rain. Rain. Help her.
[coughs]
- [alarm continues blaring]
- [♪ tense music continues]
[flesh squelching]
[gasping]
[clicking]
[whimpers]
No! [screams]
No!
[snarling]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[coughs]
Andy! Come on!
Please get up!
[grunts]
[coughs]
No!
Come on!
[wheezing]
[wheezing heavily]
[suit chimes]
[oxygen hissing]
[breathes deeply]
[doors creaking]
[roars]
"Manual Cargo Release.
Pull the four levers."
Okay. Yes.
The four levers. Okay.
One.
Two.
[rope whirring]
[panting]
[machinery cranking]
Three.
[grunts]
[automated voice]
Pull up. Pull up.
[breathing laboriously]
[sizzling]
[shrieking]
[Rain grunts]
[air whooshing]
[breathing deeply]
- [screeching]
- [Rain gasps]
[Rain screaming]
[Rain whimpering]
[helmet thuds]
[over helmet]
Die, motherfucker!
[♪ Triumphant music playing]
[♪ Solemn music playing]
I'll fix you.
[Rain] This is the cryo-log
for the mining hauler
Corbelan.
I set course
to the Yvaga system
without knowing
if I'll ever reach it,
or what fate is to find me.
But whatever comes,
I'll face it.
This is Rain Carradine,
last survivor
of the Corbelan...
signing off
[♪ music soars]
[♪ Music fades]
[♪ Tense music playing]
[♪ Suspenseful music playing]
[♪ Music fades]